An online friend request becomes a romantic journey for Samantha
Chance at Romance is a tv movie, comedy, romance film directed by Bradford May.
Samantha Hart is delighted when her online "Chance at Romance" to photographer Heath
Madsen eventually results in Heath sending her a first class ticket to visit.
Upon arriving for what she expects to be a romantic weekend, however, she learns her online relationship
with the widowed photographer was actually manufactured a matchmaking twelve year-old.
Sam is anxious to end her trip as quickly as possible, but a nasty bout
of weather extends her stay through the end of the week.
Samantha Hart, played by Erin Krakow.
Heath Madsen, played by Ryan McPartlin.
Donny Madsen, played by Ian Andrew.
Eddie, played by Albert Malafronte.
Ms. Marlow, played by Nadege August.
Bar Owner, played by Abraham Benrubi.
This is a list of interracial romance films.
The films in this list satisfy the following requirements:
A professional critic
or film scholar has identified it as an interracial romance film.
The film has been released.
The film is feature length (e.g.
not a segment from an anthology).
The film features a romantic relationship, not just
partnering, between people of different races.
The film's inclusion or casting of interracial romance is not incidental.
The film is not about romance between species or fictional races (e.g.
Star Trek, The Twilight Saga, Shrek, The Little Mermaid).
The film explores themes of photographer, matchmaking, widower, single father.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.